It's time for another paradise video and let me tell you this is the hardest paradise video I did
because this is the new pastel collection. White, pastel blue and pastel pink and if you know my
closet and my preferred colors then you probably guess what the problem was. I have no idea what
I should wear with these pants because the colors are so unusual for me I had to think
really hard and spent a lot of time thinking of outfits of what I'm going to pair with them
so I came up with a few things and I'm going to show them to you now it's just so bright and white
I think this is the first time ever that I've worn white pants
this is so weird to see me like this and I tried I tried to combine it with black but I didn't feel
it it was too harsh that contrast so the challenge is now combine all the leggings with non-black
tops and yeah pink corset and I think the pink looks a bit dim in comparison with the white
because if you pair it with the black pants it looks more pinkish does this make sense I don't
know this is just well feel like a chameleon in my set here chameleon chameleon Ted Mosby said it
like this the white stitching is of course mandatory for the white pants and it was a bit
hard to get into them I don't know why maybe because I was so afraid of the white I don't know
well if you say white is my favorite color i love white then get these pants and get 10%
off with my code zillion i'll link everything down below under the video and i'm just almost
blinded by this pants so i'm going to switch into something darker and go for the pink
and no i'm not going to combine it with a pink corset because i don't think it'll look good i
have something different it's pink and silver because I did find another sports
bra that had a matching color like a dark pink but to be honest it was really
boring so I picked this top it has a bit of black yes but there is a purple pink
shine to the sequins. Sequins was the word I was looking for here so I think it
matches really cool and on a really subtle way and I also used silver heels
to pick up the topic of the top. Okay so since I'm wearing pink pants let's do
pink light. Again I have to say I think I've never worn pink leggings before
really. I don't know if I will ever wear them again. But yeah with the blue I think it
looks good so I recommend blue hair to everyone that's the way to go you know
this outfit would be really cool to go into a new Barbie movie for cinema
because I was actually I saw the film last week I went to the cinema and it
was really cool I can really recommend it and I've seen the pictures of a lot
of my friends and random people dressing up for this movie and going to the
cinema I didn't do that but I also did not have this outfit and this pants last week so maybe I
would have done it I don't know it would have been fun okay I have one pants left blue
so let's do this and I'm really curious about that color because um I don't know how it will
with my hair I think it could be really cool I didn't try any of them on before this video
okay I feel so colorful with the red heels the blue pants actually my top is a sports bra I
just recently bought because it was on sale and I was like okay um I don't care what I wear for
sports but it was the best option I could find for this pants so I'm really happy that I have it here
I think the color of the pants is kind of cute like this baby blue and it will
probably look good with a darker colored blue top or something like that though I
like this combination too I'm not sure about the heels technically yes but it's
just a bit too colorful for me the whole pastel collection comes without a zipper
and a front for a change because I think the last few pants had all zippers but
this is the no zipper version and of course we have the signature lines here
on the sides and the nice boochy cut which makes a really cool and good
looking figure at least in my opinion so I really love to wear my paradise pants
normally just black and grey and red maybe. I don't know if I can create other
looks with these pants. I'll think about it and I'll try. Maybe you can see them
on Instagram then or you can also check out my other Paradise videos for the
black pants and all the ultra versions because they have BBC pants as well
which are really shiny so I think I have a bunch of videos online and again if you need something
and want to know something about the products leave a comment or check out the description text
and yeah I think I have nothing more to say today this was a real challenge I'm really
mentally exhausted from coming up with all these outfits and working with these unusual colors
But I made it, I pulled through and here we are.
I hope you had fun.
What do you think of the looks?
Did you like them?
Do you say no, stick with black?
Let me know in the comments.
And I'll see you in the next video.
Have a nice day.
Bye.